









Artur Korra

Download CV

About Me

Spring Security

Hello! I am Artur Korra passionate Java Software Developer with 4 years of experience. Since I started my career I have been working in enterprise desktop and web applications projects based on Java. Always open to learning new technologies.

Age 26

Email arturi25turi@gmail.com Phone +355684388951 Elbasan 3001 Albania Address

English Language

Professional Skills



XML

Spring Integration	SQL
Spring Data JPA	Docker
MySQL	Jenkins
Oracle DB	Kubernetes
Derby DB	Sonarqube
EclipseLink	Webservices REST
Hibernate	Webservices SOAP
5.11. 10.5	510
Eclipse IDE	EJB
Microservices	LDAP
Swagger	JWT

Experience

Back End Java Spring Boot Software Developer Sisal Group

Feb, 2021 - Present

Java Software Developer. Working with Spring Boot

Software Developer Freelancer

Feb, 2021 - Present

Working with different projects mostly with Spring Boot.

Java Software Developer EasyMarine

Feb. 2021 - Present

Developing desktop applications with JavaFX and maintenance support.

Full-Stack Java Software Developer EasyMarine

Feb, 2018 - Feb, 2021

Easy Marine offers digital service solutions for digitalization for the sea shipping sector. Starting from 2007 the company has built big systems for helping the crew and company office to have under control documents and different procedures requested by law. Since I started working at Easy Marine they trusted me to work on almost all company projects. Also, I have offered support to company customers.

Education

Masters in Economics Informatics from University of Aleksander Xhuvani

2017 - 2018

Modules: Web Programming (HTML, CSS, JavaScript), Object-Oriented Programming in Java, Database, Algorithm, Computer Networks, Information Security, Operating Systems, Cryptography, Computer Architecture. Master's Degree evaluation from 4-10. Result *10*.

Bachelor in Economics Informatics from University of Aleksander Xhuvani

2014 - 2017

Modules: Web Programming (HTML, CSS, JavaScript), Object-Oriented Programming in Java, Database, Algorithm, Computer Networks, Information Security, Operating Systems, Cryptography, Computer Architecture. Bachelor's Degree evaluation from 4-10. Result *9*.

Projects

Marpol Desktop APP

Oct, 2018 - Jan, 2019

Marpol is a desktop app used to calculate allowed ship pollution based on Marpol Annexes. The software calculates the allowed pollution based on the ship's location by reading shapefiles. My task was to read shapefiles based on the location of the ship and show the calculation result for allowed and not allowed emission and pollution.

Technology Stack

 ${\sf JavaFX, Equinox(OSGi), Maven, Bundle, DerbyDB, JavaFX, EclipseLink, Jasper \, Reports, GeoServer.}$

eShipManager WEB APP

Feb, 2018 - Present

EASY and EASY OFFICE ship manager. Two big web app platforms. Easy is used to the ship and EasyOffice is been used for the ship's owner's office. Two apps communicate together and transfer data between each other like documents, messages, etc. Easy and EasyOffie were existing projects and I have been working to fix different bugs also developing new modules.

Technology Stack

JavaEE, Sring Framework, JSF, Primefaces • Tomcat, MYSQL, Jasper Reports.

easymarine.it(Official Website) WEB APP

Jan, 2020 - Feb, 2020

Official Company Website that I developed all alone from scratch.

Technology Stack

 $Sring\ Boot, Thymeleaf, JavaScript, CSS, MYSQL, OpenStreetMap, KML.\ Please\ for\ more\ follow\ https://www.easymarine.it/.$

NavigationRobot WEB APP (Crawler)

Apr, 2020 - Jun, 2020

NavigationRobot is a crawler web app that is used to take information from different websites where the navigations are published. The app uses selenium for site navigation and after processing all the information generates KML files updated every week. This app I have developed all alone from scratch. Technology Stack

 $Sring\ Boot,\ Thymeleaf,\ JavaScript,\ CSS,\ MYSQL,\ OpenStreetMap,\ KML,\ Selenium.$

LogBook Desktop APP

Oct, 2019 - Oct, 2020

LogBook is a desktop app used to save ship logs operation types. Bunkering, de-bunkering, and discharging of different oils at sea is a sensitive case and regulated by law. LogBook is used to save all logs as the law request it. On this project, I have been working with my team leader and we developed it from scratch.

Technology Stack

JavaFX, Equinox(OSGi), Maven, Bundle, DerbyDB, JavaFX, EclipseLink, Jasper Reports.

Smartload Desktop APP

Oct, 2020 - Present

Smart Load is a desktop app used to calculate ship stability at sea based on tank weight, volume filled, tank types, tanks position, and ships specifications. On this project, I have been working with my team leader and we developed it from scratch.

Technology Stack

JavaFX, Equinox(OSGi), Maven, Bundle, DerbyDB, JavaFX, EclipseLink, Jasper Reports.

Notices To Mariners Desktop APP

Apr, 2021 - Present

The app downloads "Notices to Mariners" published on the official UK FTP and merges all the information to save the data as an inventory for each different ship that will use the app. I developed this app by myself from scratch.

Technology Stack

JavaFX, Equinox(OSGi), Maven, Bundle, DerbyDB, JavaFX, EclipseLink, Jasper Reports.

Atena (Gambling) Web App

Feb, 2021 - Present

Working with spring boot and microservice.

Technology Stack

JDK 11, Maven, Spring Boot, LDAP, JWT, ReactJS, Oracle DB, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Sonarqube.

Atena-Admin (Gambling-BackOffice) Web App

Feb, 2021 - Present

Working with spring boot and microservice.

Technology Stack

JDK 11, Maven, Spring Boot, LDAP, JWT, ReactJS, Oracle DB, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Sonarqube.

Sogei (Gambling) Web App

Feb, 2021 - Present

Working with spring boot and microservice.

Technology Stack

 $EJB, Maven, Spring\ Boot, LDAP, JWT, ReactJS, Oracle\ DB, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Sonarqube.$

Wallet (Gambling) Web App

Working with spring boot and microservice.

Technology Stack

JDK 11, Maven, Spring Boot, LDAP, JWT, ReactJS, Oracle DB, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Sonarqube.

REGISTRY (Gambling) Web App

Feb, 2021 - Present

Working with spring boot and microservice.

Technology Stack

JDK 11, Maven, Spring Boot, LDAP, JWT, ReactJS, Oracle DB, Docker, Kubernetes, Jenkins, Sonarqube.

My Coin Api (BackEnd) and My Coin (FrontEnd) Web App

Feb, 2021 - Present

Online demo for testing API:

 $\underline{https://my\text{-}coin\text{-}api.herokuapp.com/my\text{-}coin\text{-}api/swagger-ui.html}\#/$

Online Next-JS APP connected to BackEnd:

https://my-coin-arturkorra.vercel.app/

This is a demo project not yet completed that stimulates how a crypto wallet and exchange should work. Technology Stack

JDK 11, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Spring Data, JWT, Hibernet, Swagger and Maven

My Coin (FrontEnd)

HTML, CSS, Javascript with NEXT JS Framework (React Js)

Contact

Address

Elbasan 3001 Albania

Phone

+355684388951

Email

arturi25turi@gmail

Artur Korra





